techdigest.tv 2009-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Shiny Media

**The blog you've been reading is part of Shiny Media. Shiny Media is committed to protecting your privacy.**

This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. 

You can visit any of our blogs without disclosing any personally identifiable information about yourself. 

By using this blog or submitting information to us through or in connection with this Blog, you signify your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you must not use this Blog or submit information to us through or in connection with this Blog.

* The information we collect and how we use it

When you choose to provide us with any personal information that relates to and identifies you, including but not limited to your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, you consent to us using this information to send you details of special offers, competitions and news about the site you have subscribed to or the wider section of which it forms a part (Sport, Technology, Fashion, Games or Tech).

We will use, store or otherwise process any information collected on registration, or through survey participation or competition entry to the extent reasonably necessary to provide the services that are available through our Blog to you by us (for the purpose of this Privacy Policy, the term 'services' also includes products).

We process this information for the purpose of: 

  * dealing with your inquiries and requests, including contacting you where necessary;
  * providing and personalising our services; 
  * providing you access to all parts of the Blog;
  * administering registration and membership records;
  * carrying out market research campaigns; and
  * improving and developing the Blog and our services.

We also gather this information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring Blog usage and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify you.

We may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Blog or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to let you know about other products and services which we offer (either independently or jointly with or on behalf of other organisations) which may be of interest to you and we may contact you by post, telephone, fax, as well as by email. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know.

If you choose to post messages in our forum or other message areas (where we provide such capability on the Blog), we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

If you stop using the Blog or your permission to use the Blog is terminated, we may continue to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time) and as permitted by law. However, if you wish us to stop e-mailing you with information in connection with the Blog, please send your request in accordance with paragraph 4 below.

* Information security 

The Internet is not a secure medium. However, we have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy. 

Where you have been allocated a user admin area, this area is protected by your user name and password, which you should never divulge to anyone else.

Please be aware that communications over the Internet, such as emails/webmails are not secure unless they have been encrypted. Your communications may route through a number of countries before being delivered - this is the nature of the World Wide Web/Internet. We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control. 

We believe that we have appropriate policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control (having regard to the type and amount of that data) from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. 

All of our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with, the processing of your personal information are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' information. 

We ensure that your information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if required by law or when requested to by regulatory bodies or law enforcement organisations. 

* To whom will your information be disclosed?

Your information may, for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, be disclosed for processing to: 

  * our employees;
  * our affiliates; 
  * our group companies and their employees;
  * successors in title to our business; 
  * third party consultants, contractors or other service providers who may access your personal information when providing services (including but not limited to IT support services) to us; 
  * government bodies and law enforcement agencies and in response to other legal and regulatory requests; 
  * auditors or contractors or other advisers auditing, assisting with or advising on any of our business purposes,
  * where you have consented to this, to carefully selected third parties that may contact you about products and services which may be of interest to you. Unless we specify otherwise at the point of sign up we will not share your details with anyone else.

* Your rights in relation to your information

You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your information and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Where appropriate, you may have your personal information erased, rectified, amended or completed. Please write to Shiny Media, 20-22 Stukeley St, WC2B 5LR.

Please quote your name and address. We should be grateful if you would also provide brief details of the information of which you would like a copy or which you would like to be corrected (this helps us to more readily locate your data). 

We will require proof of your identity before providing you with details of any personal information we may hold about you. We may charge a fee of £10 to cover the administration costs involved in providing you with a copy of your information. 

You can opt out of receiving information from us at any time and we will promptly deal with your request. You can unsubscribe by either clicking the **_'Unsubscribe'_** link at the bottom of the email you receive, emailling [info@shinymedia.com](mailto:info@shinymedia.com) with 'UNSUBSCRIBE' in the subject line or writing to us at 20-22 Stukeley St, London, WC2B 5LR

. 
* Cookies

Pieces of information transferred to your computer's hard disk from a blog are known as cookies. They allow our Blog to store information about your browsing patterns, making the Blog more useful to you. They may be placed by us or a third party to collect information in the course of ads being served on our sites. Many major sites use cookies: in fact, they are commonly used throughout the Internet to offer personalised services. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. Each time you use our Blog, the cookie is accessed. This way, we can track the features you use and the pages and content that you view on the Blog to help personalise your experience. The information we collect will not be associated with any personally identifying information. Where you are allocated log-in details, we may also use cookies (but only if you so choose) to let you automatically log-in to the Blog so that you do not have to re-enter your email and/or password each time you visit. You may disable cookie support on your browser but be aware that by doing so, you may lose certain features that require a cookie to work properly. We may use the information collected by the cookie to provide us with various statistics without identifying any individual. 

Please contact us at info@shinymedia.com if you require information about disabling any cookies on the Blog.

* Your consent and changes to this Privacy Policy

By submitting any personal information (including, without limitation, your payment details) to us you consent to the use of information as set out in this policy. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy and if we do so we will post the changes on this page. It is your responsibility to check the Privacy Policy every time you submit information to us or place an order. Use will signify that you agree to any such changes.

In the event the purposes for processing change, then we will contact you as soon as practicable and seek your consent where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing.

Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area. Countries outside of the EEA may not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try and protect the security of your information.

* Use of your personal information submitted to other blogs

We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you accessed the third party site using links from our Blog. 

We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact the owner or operator of such blog if you have concerns or questions. 

* Further information

For further information from us on data protection and privacy or any requests concerning your personal information please write to Shiny Media, 20-22 Stukeley St, London WC2B 5LR. or email us at info@shinymedia.com
